(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T22:16:51.461106",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
Attention: For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
hololive Dreams
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: For Visitors]
PENLIGHT COLORS
事前登録受付中！
[Pre-registration Now Open!]
ローソンにお越しのみなさん！
Everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson Campaign Confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These six will appear this time!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details scheduled to be released on March 9 (Mon)!
いっしょにバンダイナムコブース、大好き！
Let's go to the Bandai Namco booth together! I love it!
注目の新商品も初公開！
Our featured new products will be revealed for the first time!
会場限定スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue-exclusive special photo booth!
あなただけのカードデザイン！
Your very own card design!
限定カードももらえる！
You can also get exclusive cards!
展示ブースでも大公開！
Also on display at the exhibition booth!
体感せよ！
Experience it!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over again.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now, let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ (hey！！) hey！！ (hey！！)
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!)
yeah！！
Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream,
想像できないような
into something unimaginable,
想いになったんだ
it has become our feelings.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement never stops!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes a ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it away!
果てない旅路を今
An endless journey, right now,
漕いでる途中にあるでしょう
we must be in the middle of rowing.
それも力に変えて
Turning even that into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
let's move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい<
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you is...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, my treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our destination,
あの日に誓ったんだ
we swore on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve will not waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
"I must do this right!" pushing my back,
明日への橋になる
becoming a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is "taken for granted."
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めたらいいのかもがいて
struggling with where to even begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
little by little, we gathered in a circle and found
何にも代えられない夢だ
this dream that cannot be replaced.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the incomplete parts.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even if it's a tiny hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always,
馬鹿にされても
even if others make fun of us,
信じたい！
believe in it!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ<
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll always be together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you is...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, my treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times, I will stand up,
笑い合っていたい
I want to keep smiling with you.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！<
Our wishes too, let's make them together!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ (hey！！) hey！！ (hey！！)
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!)
yeah！！
Yeah!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly. Please wait a moment.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
Please beware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration is now open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there...
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう!
Come on, let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a tiny dream...
想像できないような
that was beyond imagination...
想いになったんだ
it became a feeling.
わくわく止まらない!
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost...
絆が船になる
our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now...
漕いでる途中に出会う困難もあるでしょう
we will surely face difficulties along the way,
それも力に変えて
but we'll turn those into strength too...
一緒に進むんだよ!
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there...
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't just end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too...
「らしく」輝いていたい
and keep shining in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, getting to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, because you are my treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map.
まだまだ行こう!
Let's keep going on and on!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind...
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our destination...
あの日に誓ったんだ
we made a promise on that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve will never waver!
「ちゃんとしなきゃ!」って背中
The back that says "I have to do this right!"...
明日への橋になる
will become a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We must cherish it even more...
「あたりまえ」無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a small ship...
どっから始めたらいいのかもがいて
struggling with where we should even begin.
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Gradually forming a circle, we found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that nothing else can replace!
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even our incompleteness...
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our thoughts are as one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with just a tiny sliver of hope...
僕と君でずっと
you and I will go on forever.
馬鹿にされても
Even if others make fun of us...
信じたい!
we want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is simply not enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are just overflowing...
ずっと一緒だよ!
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there...
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't just end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too...
「らしく」輝いていたい
and keep shining in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, getting to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, because you are my treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map...
まだまだ行けるから!
because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times, we'll stand back up...
笑い合っていたいたい
and keep laughing together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ!
Everyone together with our wishes, come on!
手をつないで想像も超えて
Let's hold hands and go beyond our imagination...
まだまだ行こう!
Let's keep going on and on!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
角巻わため 大好き
[Towel: I love Tsunomaki Watame]
ころねすきー
[Bag: Koronesuki]
雪民
[Doll Shirt: Yukimin]
天音かなた
[Banner: Amane Kanata]
BAU BAU かいな
[Headband: BAU BAU, right?]
Pledge of Loyalty
[Certificate: Pledge of Loyalty]
にゃんぐまーんは姉妹 / おーい！ / お疲れ！
[Tablet: Nyangmar is sisters / Hey! / Good job!]
ホロリス各位！声出してけ～！
[Tablet: To all Holo-listeners! Make some noise~!]
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハモり重ねた言葉
Words layered in harmony...
届いて
...please reach you!
お互い少し照れては
Embarrassed, we look at each other,
ぎこちないと笑ってた
and laugh about how awkward we are.
未来予想 あの日の
The future we envisioned...
続きを見よう
...let's see what lies ahead of that day.
手と手繋いで
Holding hands,
風も引きこなして
harnessing even the wind,
扉を叩いて
knocking on the door,
連れて行くよ
I'll take you there.
どんなこともきっと
No matter what happens,
一緒なら怖くない
we're not afraid if we're together.
乗り越えていけ
Let's overcome it!
La la la la...
鳴り止まない 希望のメロディー
A never-ending melody of hope.
ほら、らららら
Look, la la la la...
聞こえてる 聞こえてる
I hear it, I hear it...
歌
This song!
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Our harmony, the words we piled up,
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond those brilliant days...
いつだって君と 一歩一歩
Always with you, step by step,
彩るストーリー
Painting our story.
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Our harmony, the dreams we tied together,
空へ 駆けてゆく
Soar up into the sky.
きらめきに乗せて
Carried on the sparkles,
あなたへ
toward you...
届け メロディ
Reach them, oh melody,
どこまでも
to the ends of the earth!
何気ないことを思い出す
I remember those casual moments,
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
taking a deep breath to remind myself I'm not alone.
見たい景色 楽しむ魔法の言葉
The magic words that let me enjoy the scenery I wanted to see.
ふと気がついて ふと振り返って
Suddenly realizing, suddenly looking back,
また君を知って その度に
I get to know you again, and every time,
ちょっと勇気出して
I muster a little courage,
明日へと飛び込んでいける
and dive right into tomorrow.
らららら
La la la la...
降り積もる道標はまだ
The accumulating signposts are still...
らららら
La la la la...
微笑んでいる
...smiling.
歌
This song!
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
Our harmony, when we reach out our hands,
足元に虹がかかる
a rainbow appears under our feet.
いつか晴れる
Someday it will clear up,
口ずさんだステージ
on this stage we sing along to.
ハーモニー 記した場所へ
Our harmony, towards the place we marked,
運ぶ 約束を
carrying our promise.
輝きに乗せて
Riding on the radiance,
世界へ
to the world...
響いて メロディ
Resound, oh melody,
いつまでも
forever!
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step we took together, that very moment,
宝物だって胸を張る今
I can proudly call it a treasure now.
輝き出して 笑顔がゆくから
It begins to shine, because our smiles are on their way,
色褪せないまま
without ever fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Look, our voices blend together...
聞こえてる 聞こえてる
I hear it, I hear it...
歌
This song!
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Our harmony, the words we piled up,
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond those brilliant days...
いつだって君と 一歩一歩
Always with you, step by step,
彩るストーリー
Painting our story.
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Our harmony, the dreams we tied together,
空へ 駆けてゆく
Soar up into the sky.
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
Carried on the sparkles, toward you...
世界へ
To the world...
響いて
Resound!
愛も メロディ
Our love and melody,
どこまでも
to the ends of the earth!
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We will shine,
呼び合う声を合図に
with our calling voices as the signal!
パレパレパレ 探しにゆく
Parade, Parade, Parade! We'll go search for it,
スタートは何度だって
starting over as many times as it takes!
ただ独り言を綴った
I weave lonely words into echoes,
ただ始まりたくて走った
I run because I want to start anew.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Far away, lighting up the darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
it's a name that shines so brilliantly.
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Memories filled with too much kindness...
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out, wanting to get closer,
思いがけず結び合った
and unexpectedly, we connected.
ほら 今
Look, now,
迷子は “僕等” になった
the lost ones have become "us."
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We will shine,
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
bring along your frustrations and your love!
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can fly high!
ささやかな祈りは光
Our humble prayers will turn into light.
終わりなき軌跡
An endless path...
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can be proud to have found you...
心から
...from the bottom of my heart...
これから
...from now on.
アワ・ブライト・パレード！パレード！
Our Bright Parade! Parade!
頼りない予感を
Let's sing...
歌おう
...of this fragile premonition.
恥ずかしくなんてないよ
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can undo,
いつかまた会えるおまじない
a spell to meet again someday.
あの日ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero on that day.
数えきれないことばかり
With so many countless memories,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
they're not something you can just count.
ほら今 僕らを 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now, let's call us one!
パレード！パレード！手と手 繋いだよ
Parade! Parade! We've joined hand in hand.
許し合える 刹那 夜はきらめく
The moment we accept each other, the night sparkles.
雨晴れ晴れ また来ない空
Rain or shine, a sky that won't come again...
繰り返した日々とは 君とあることさ
...those repeated days were all spent with you.
君とあることなんだ
They were spent with you!
ただいまを聞けば
When I hear "I'm home..."
おかえりって叫ぶよ
...I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to take for granted.
パレード！パレード！輝くんだよ
Parade! Parade! Let's shine!
暗がりを満たすのは 君と僕だ
The ones filling the darkness are you and I.
パレード！パレード！高鳴るんだよ
Parade! Parade! Our hearts are pounding!
悔しさも 愛しさも 全て抱いて
Embracing all the frustration and love,
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
we can soar on the wind, dreams, and wings.
ささやかな祈りばかり 終わりなき軌跡
An endless path filled with simple prayers,
君と飛び込んで行く 素敵なスタートさ
we'll dive into a wonderful start together.
ここから
From here,
これから アワ・ブライト・パレード！パレード！
from now on. Our Bright Parade! Parade!
アワ・ブライト・パレード！パレード！
Our Bright Parade! Parade!
メインステージも盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's heat up the main stage as well!
ステージは最初から飛ばしていくぞ！
We're going full throttle on stage from the very start!
1 2 3カウント 合わせ ワン ツー
1, 2, 3 count, line up, one-two.
揃う手と手 揃った時に見えたっしょ
When our hands joined, you saw it, didn't you?
焦がしてっせ ああ ぶちかますフェイク
We're burning it up, yeah, pulling off a fake,
焦るな敵視 必勝 ごきげんラッキー
don't rush, hostility, certain victory, feeling lucky!
捕らえろ熱狂
Seize the frenzy!
1 2 3カウント ココア割って一杯
1, 2, 3 count, let's mix a cup of cocoa!
天下無双 フレーバー抜群 ゲート開けてどうぞ
Peerless flavor, unmatched, open the gates, please.
繰り返すダンスフロアのビート 一生絶好調
Repeatedly on the dance floor beat, always at our best,
見せてあげるよ 完膚なきまでの勝利法
I'll show you an absolute way to win!
一つ二つ 決まる勝敗
One, two, the outcome is decided.
この世界中を 手の内に収めるまで
Until I hold this entire world in my hands.
Draw in the night My ambition
こぼしたアイス 溶け出したアイス
Spilled ice, melting ice.
You know I gotcha! みんなパーティー
You know I gotcha! Everyone, let's party!
今もずっとおマジックショー
Still ongoing, the magic show!
全部ラッキー 逆転 狙いじゃん
Everything's lucky, aiming for a comeback.
ハイ & ロー で踊り狂え
Dance wildly high and low,
届け この メロディー
let this melody reach you.
1 2 3 4 鳴らせ ストーリー
1, 2, 3, 4, sound out the story.
愛して、愛して、ゲームオン
Love me, love me, game on!
Get set, call me the giant
Put everything on the line
So you calling me up
That's why I get ya!
Everybody panic
心配は what's up magic...
Worries? What's up, magic...
絶対じゃつまらない
Certainty is boring
Let's win, 止まらないわ
Let's win, I won't stop
Let's count, なんちゃって dramatic...
Let's count, just kidding, dramatic...
そう一口味わったら最後
Yes, once you get a taste, it's over
決めるわ match point
I'll decide it, match point
Shine, spade, take it home
勝者の行く末 待つは滅亡か
The victor's fate—is it ruin that awaits?
勝負のコール ここからさ
The call of the match, it starts here
One more breath, light up the road
One more breath in the sun
This game's only just begun!
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna get get get
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna...
溢れる欲望 導くままに
Led by overflowing desires...
溺れず降臨する私
I descend without drowning in them
サクサクサクセス I embody
S-S-Success, I embody
It's a habit when I make everybody yell
High low, high low
Let's win, 止まらないわ
Let's win, I won't stop
High or low, dealing magic...
狂気の上で踊り狂うこの鼓動
This heartbeat dancing wildly on madness
決めるわ match point
I'll decide it, match point
さあ get get down
Now, get get down
Spade, spade, club, 勝負あり
Spade, spade, club, game set
I'm getting lucky tonight
Get lucky, spade, club, spade, heart
思うままに理想を描いたような勝利を take it home
Bringing home a victory exactly as I ideally envisioned
take it home
Mococo, ready? Ready!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you, I want to be with you!
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! Bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright 二人は
Yeah, future is bright, the two of us
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Mococo! Fuwawa!
My heart and soul and tail are Fuwawa
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
I love being tricky, doggie kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
Fuwamoco together, take us along with you!
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたい 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you, I want to be with you!
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! Bau bau!
一生涯 sing with you
A lifetime of singing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
It's showtime, 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, I want to be with you!
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! Bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright 二人は
Yeah, future is bright, the two of us
Fluffy, fuzzy, yappy sisters!
Bau! Woo! Bau! Woo! Bau!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy-dog kept sealed away
'bout a burst, fluff and fuzz, we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement, dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin', but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreparable
We're a pair, unbreakable!
And that's why, いつだって, it's that day
And that's why, always, it's that day
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
一生涯 walk with you
A lifetime of walking with you
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter!
いつだって, it's that day
Always, it's that day
Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday! Bau bau!
Yeah, 二人は happy, lucky, puppy sisters!
Yeah, the two of us are happy, lucky, puppy sisters!
Fuwamoco, bau bau!
Everyday, bau-bau! Hallo, hallo, bau bau!
Everyday, bau-bau!
ダメダメ ノンノン, don't touch the ears!
No no, non-non, don't touch the ears!
もふもふ ノンノン, don't touch the tail!
Fluffy fluffy, non-non, don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ Fuwawaだよ, bau!
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa, bau!
Fuwawaじゃないよ Mococoだよ, bau!
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo, bau!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah, bau!
And together we're Fuwamoco!
Gather up our dreams and suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams, we don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever together here with you!
It's showtime, 一緒にいたい (fu-fu!)
It's showtime, I want to be with you (fu-fu!)
It's showtime, 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, I want to be with you!
Fuwa-fuwa, moco-moco, hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it, won't forget our pledge with you
It's showtime, 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, I want to be with you!
Lifetime! Showtime! Anytime! Bau bau!
一生涯 sing with you
A lifetime of singing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
Sweet time 欲しいの
...sweet time, I want it.
あぁカミサマどうして
Oh God, why...
好きになるほど Dream night 切ないの
is it so painful to fall in love during Dream Night?
とっておきの クマちゃん出したし
I even took out my precious teddy bear,
今夜は大丈夫かな？
so will I be alright tonight?
ラスト行くよー！
Let's go for the last part!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
フワモコバウ フワモコバウバウ！
Fuwamoco Bau! Fuwamoco Bau Bau!
オーバー！
Over!
誰がなんと言おうと、今日はクリスマス...
No matter what anyone says, today is Christmas...
これは、キミとの、約束の物語...
This is a story of a promise with you...
「ぺこチキン、いかがぺこか～!?」
"Would you like some Peko Chicken-peko!?"
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
らっしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さぁさぁ今日も元気に焼いて焼いて焼いちゃって
Now, now, happily roasting, roasting, roasting again today!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人飛んでパーティー様
Loner customers, organizers, and even those partying all alone!
どうでしょう一つぺこチキン
How about a Peko Chicken?
えっさほいさ焼き上げろ
Heave-ho, bake it up!
あっちゅー間に行列だ
In a blink of an eye, there's a long line!
レジの向こう お腹空腹中
Across the register, hungry bellies...
待たせてsorry
Sorry to keep you waiting!
てんやわんやしちゃうケド
Though things get pretty hectic,
キチンとね仕上げるゾ
I'll make sure to finish them properly!
迸る秘伝のスパイス
Squirting out secret spices,
ラブアンドピース
Love and Peace!
美味しくなれなれ 唱えて
Cast a spell, "Become delicious!"
じっくりじっくり こんがりこんがり
Slowly, slowly, golden brown, golden brown
ギラッとカラッと輝いて
Shining bright and crispy!
ほかほかシャキーン！
Steaming hot and sharp!
変身だ！
Transform!
お待たせぺこ！喰らえ！
Thanks for waiting-peko! Dig in!
やめらんねーよ やめらんねーよ ぺこチキン
Can't stop, can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ とんでもねーよ ぺこチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable Peko Chicken!
パリッとジュワッとホロッとたっぷりアツアツ
Crispy, juicy, tender, plenty hot!
ほらお一つどうでしょう？
Look, won't you have one?
やめらんねーな やめらんねーな ぺこチキン
Can't stop, can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーな とんでもねーな ぺこチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable Peko Chicken!
ガブッとバリッとクラッと にんまり ぺろり
Bite hard, crunch away, light-headed (smiling, licking lips)
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
This deliciousness is driving me crazy!
いっちょお届け
Deliver one order!
ぜったいお届け
Definitely deliver it!
お待たせぺこ！
Thanks for waiting-peko!
冷めたらチンしてぺこチキン
Heat it up if it gets cold, Peko Chicken!
あーあー、この度はご来店いただき、
Ah, ah, thank you very much for coming
誠に、誠にありがとうございます。
to our shop today.
本日も元気に焼いておりますのは、
What we are energetically roasting today is
肉汁脳汁たっぷり！ぺこチキンでございます。
juicy and brain-melting! It's Peko Chicken.
熱く、こんがり、冷やさないをモットーに
With our motto, "hot, golden-brown, never cold,"
ジューシーバリバリ、ジューシーバリバリ取り揃えております。
we have a crispy and juicy selection ready.
みなさまの、日頃のご愛顧に感謝を込めて。
With gratitude for your daily patronage...
ただいまより、チキンフィーバータイム突入とさせていただきます。
...we will now enter Chicken Fever Time!
それでは、お呼び出しを申し上げます。
And now, we will call out the orders.
アツアツチキンの客様ー？（はーい！）
Hot chicken customers? (Yes!)
お一人ぼっちのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Single, lonely customers? (Yes!)
自称パーティーピープルのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Self-proclaimed party people customers? (Yes!)
骨なしチキンのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Boneless chicken customers? (Yes!)
ハニーシロップランドシップのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Honey syrup round-ship customers? (Yes!)
ニクアブラマシマシカラメのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Extra meat, fat, and strong sauce customers? (Yes!)
限界突破完凸希望のお客様ー？（はーい！）
Limit break max-dupe wishing customers? (Yes!)
お腹ぺこぺこのお客様ー？（はーい！）
Very hungry customers? (Yes!)
聖なる夜には？
On this holy night...
...on this holy night!
どこでも向かうよぺこチキン
I will go anywhere, Peko Chicken!
遅くなってごめんね
Sorry for being late.
やっと言えた世界で
In a world where I could finally say it,
冷えた孤独を温めたげる
I'll warm up your cold loneliness.
一人じゃないよもう
You're not alone anymore.
冷めた食卓に彩りを。それが、聖なるぺこチキン！
Color to a cold dinner table. That is the holy Peko Chicken!
だからだから
That's why, that's why...
お腹ぺこぺこぺこぺこチキン！
Hungry, hungry, hungry, hungry chicken!
だから
That's why...
やめらんねーよ やめらんねーよ ぺこチキン
Can't stop, can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
暗えなびらねえな ぺこチキン
Unbelievable, unbelievable Peko Chicken!
パリッとジュワッとホロッとたっぷりアツアツ
Crispy, juicy, tender, plenty hot!
ほらもう一つどうでしょう？
Look, won't you have another one?
冷めちゃヤダ冷めちゃヤダ ぺこチキン
No cold ones, no cold ones, Peko Chicken!
あっためなきゃあっためなきゃ ぺこチキン
Must heat it up, must heat it up, Peko Chicken!
ガブッとバリッとクラッと にんまり ぺろり
Bite hard, crunch away, light-headed (smiling, licking lips)
おかしくなっちゃう 美味しさ
This deliciousness is driving me crazy!
めちゃお届け
Delivering so much!
すっごいお届け
Delivering incredibly!
お待たせぺこ！今夜は一緒にぺこチキン
Thanks for waiting-peko! Tonight, let's have Peko Chicken together!
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
らっしゃいませ らっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さぁさぁ今日も元気に焼いて焼いて焼いちゃって
Now, now, happily roasting, roasting, roasting again today!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人飛んでパーティー様
Loner customers, organizers, and even those partying all alone!
どうでしょう一つぺこチキン
How about a Peko Chicken?
ぺこチキン
Peko Chicken!
白上フブキ
[Shirakami Fubuki]
不知火フレア
[Shiranui Flare]
角巻わため
[Tsunomaki Watame]
尾丸ポルカ
[Omaru Polka]
バカタレサーカス、参上！
Bakatare Circus is here!
さあ行くよー！せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set, go!
Are you ready four! Agete ke foo!!
Are you ready, four! Raise it up, foo!!
超弩級のバカのおでまし (Go go!)
Here comes the super-dreadnought fools! (Go go!)
Are you ready four! Agete ke foo!!
Are you ready, four! Raise it up, foo!!
宴の合図 叫びましょう
It's the signal for the feast, let's scream!
Yeah!!!!!
みんな、お待たせー！
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting!
我々の出番だ！
It's our turn now!
最高に盛り上げていくから！
We're going to hype this up to the max!
楽しんでいってねー！
Have a great time!
始まるよ Suddenly
It's starting suddenly.
思い立ったなら Nice day! (Nice day!)
If you just think of it, it's a nice day! (Nice day!)
ノープランでも駆け抜けろ (Oh oh oh)
Even with no plan, run through! (Oh oh oh)
遊び疲れたら
If you get tired from playing,
温かなお茶で Break time (Break time)
take a break time with warm tea! (Break time)
メリハリつけて楽しみ尽くそう
Keep a good balance and enjoy it to the fullest.
好奇心は止まらない
Our curiosity won't stop.
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
I wonder what kind of story is waiting for us.
Are you ready four! Agete ke foo!!
Are you ready, four! Raise it up, foo!!
バカなこと起こすお祭りだ
It's a festival for making foolish things happen!
Make it loud この瞬間をバカ騒ごう
Make it loud, let's go crazy in this moment!
ハチャメチャ劇ノリが大事
An off-the-wall, dramatic vibe is what matters!
遠慮なんていらないよ
No need to hold back at all!
One two jump 果てしなく飛べ
One, two, jump, fly endlessly!
思いのまま
Just as your heart desires.
青春とは刹那的さ
Youth is but a fleeting moment,
楽しむしかないじゃん
so we might as well enjoy it!
不揃いなままで通じ合う
Even mismatching, we understand each other.
私達が Best friends!
We are best friends!
一番デカイ声出せ (Go go!)
Let out your loudest voice! (Go go!)
またとないこの機会を (Go go!)
Don't miss this one-of-a-kind chance! (Go go!)
とんでもねぇ、待ってたんだ (Go go!)
Unbelievable, I've been waiting for this! (Go go!)
やいのやいの相も変わらない! (わー!)
Noisy as always, nothing's changed! (Whoa!)
まだまだ声出せるよねー？行くよー！せーの！
You can still make some noise, right? Here we go! One, two!
Are you ready four! Agete ke foo!!
Are you ready, four! Raise it up, foo!!
バカなこと起こすお祭りだ
It's a festival for making foolish things happen!
Vividな Stampede 集まり超 laugh in
A vivid stampede, gathering and laughing out loud.
最骨頂の時間を ほら Gimme gimme more!
Look, this is the peak of our time! Gimme, gimme more!
Nobody's fool! みんなで叫ぼうぜ
Nobody's fool! Let's all scream together!
愛込めて せーの
With love, ready...
バカタレサーカス!!!!
"Bakatare Circus!!!!"
好奇心は終わらない
Our curiosity will never end.
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
I wonder what kind of story is waiting for us.
大切なこの瞬間を分かち合おう
Let's share this precious moment.
紡いできた思い出をさ
The memories we've woven together...
飾り付けして さぁ
...let's decorate them now!
Make it loud この瞬間をバカ騒ごう
Make it loud, let's go crazy in this moment!
ハチャメチャ劇ノリが大事
An off-the-wall, dramatic vibe is what matters!
遠慮なんていらないよ
No need to hold back at all!
One two jump 果てしなく飛べ
One, two, jump, fly endlessly!
思いのまま
Just as your heart desires.
青春とは刹那的さ
Youth is but a fleeting moment,
楽しむしかないじゃん
so we might as well enjoy it!
がむしゃらがずっとお似合いさ
Being reckless always suits us best.
私達はまだはしゃぐよ Hands up!!!!!
We're still going to mess around! Hands up!!!!!
私達は
We are...
まだはしゃぐよ
...going to keep playing around...
ハチャメチャー！
...like crazy!
Lalalalala...
Yeah!
盛り上がってくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for hyping things up!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
まだまだたくさん盛り上がってねー！
Keep having an amazing time, okay?!
みんな、ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much, everyone!
バカタレサーカスのオリジナル曲、皆さんありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much for listening to Bakatare Circus's original song!
ということでちょっとね、皆さん！
So now, everyone!
コールアンドレスポンスもしたいと思います！
I'd like to do a call-and-response!
これも兼ねましてね、
Along with that...
自己紹介タイム、やっていきましょうか！
let's do our self-introductions!
お願いします！
Please do!
白上フブキ！
Shirakami Fubuki!
はい、白上からいきます。皆さん、白上が
Okay, I'll go first. Everyone, when I say
「コーンコーンきつね！」って言ったら、
"Kon Kon Kitsune!",
「コーンコーンきつね！」で返してください。いけますか？
please reply with "Kon Kon Kitsune!". Ready?
いけます！
Ready!
はい、ではいきますよ。
Okay, here we go.
皆さん、コーンコーンきつね！
Everyone, Kon Kon Kitsune!
コーンコーンきつね！
Kon Kon Kitsune!
これもやっとくか。
Should I do this one too?
ふわふわしっぽのご馳走！
Fluffy tail feast!
あなたの心のナンバーワン、どっこいしょ！
Number one in your heart, Dokkoisho!
白上フブキです！
It's Shirakami Fubuki!
はい、フレンド！
Hi, friends!
ま、フェスだからね、やっときましょう。
Well, since it's a festival, I had to do it.
次はフレア！
Next is Flare!
フレア！
Flare!
はい、じゃあ、私が「ハイダーリン！」って言ったら、
Okay, then when I say "Hi Darling!",
「ハイハイハニー！」って返してください。
please reply with "Hi Hi Honey!"
世界で一番？って聞くんで、
I'll ask "Number one in the world?",
「愛してる！」って返してください。
so reply with "I love you!"
オッケー？
Okay?
じゃあ、いきますよ。
Here we go.
ハイダーリン！
Hi Darling!
ハイハイハニー！
Hi Hi Honey!
世界で一番？
Number one in the world?
愛してる！
I love you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Generation, Shiranui Flare!
お次は？
Next is?
みんなわかるよね？
Everyone knows, right?
お、なんだろう。なんだなんだ。
Oh, what is it? What, what?
ホロライブ4期生、
Hololive 4th Generation...
角巻…
Tsunomaki...
わため！
Watame!
ちょっと、今ちょっと惑わあったな。
Wait, there was a bit of confusion just now.
違うだろ。
That's not it!
角巻…！
Tsunomaki...!
わため！
Watame!
わためナンバーワン！
Watame number one!
煽りが雑。そんなのありなの？
That was so lazy. Is that allowed?
どどどどどど！
Dododododo!
ホロライブ4期生、角巻わためです！
Hololive 4th Generation, Tsunomaki Watame!
そして、
And...
ね、思ったんだけど、あれじゃないの？今のは。
Hey, I was thinking, wasn't it supposed to be...
わためのコールってさ、
Watame's call, like...
「こんばん…」
"Konban..."
「ドドド」だと思った。
"Dododo", I thought.
いつもの挨拶忘れるなよ！
Don't forget the usual greeting!
お疲れ様です！
Good job!
ということで、尾丸ポルカが「ポルカおるかー？」って言ったら
So, when Omaru Polka says "Is Polka here?",
「おるよー！」って言ってほしいな。
I want you to say "She's here!"
いくよ！ポルカおるかー？！
Here we go! Is Polka here?!
おるよー！
She's here!
ホロライブ5期生、ねぽらぼのぽ、
Hololive 5th Generation, Nepolabo's "Po",
尾丸ポルカです！よろしくお願いします！
Omaru Polka! Pleased to meet you!
すごい、締まってる。
Amazing, so organized.
いいね、いい感じ。
Nice, looking good.
どう？皆さん、声出てる感じですか？
How is it? Does everyone sound like they've got their voices going?
いやね、まだ足りないよ、声がちょっと。
No, it's still not enough, your voices.
確かに。
True.
まだ行けるよね？！
You can still go, right?!
始まったばっかりだもんな！
We've only just begun!
そうだそうだ！声出して行こう！
That's right, that's right! Let's raise our voices!
そしたら、こっちが「盛り上がってるか？！」って聞くんで、
Then, we'll ask "Are you hyped?!",
「うおおお！」とか「いぇーい！」とか言ってください。
so say "Uohhhhh!" or "Yeah!"
いくよ、みんな。せーの！
Here we go, everyone. One, two...
盛り上がってるかー？！
Are you hyped?!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあ、あれもやろうよ、ウェーブ。
Then let's also do that, the wave.
あ、やろう、やろう！
Ah, let's do it, let's do it!
ウェーブ行っちゃう？波作る？
Shall we do the wave? Make a wave?
めちゃめちゃ珍しい時間使おう、我々。
Let's use this extremely rare time of ours.
早く早く。
Quickly, quickly.
じゃあ、こっちからウェーブいきますよ！
Okay, the wave will start from this side!
ペンライト振って、手もいいよ、なんでもいい。
Wave your penlights, hands are fine too, anything.
お友達の皆さん、出航！
To all our friends, setting sail!
せーの！
One, two...
すげえ！
Amazing!
よくできました！ありがとうございます！
Well done! Thank you very much!
やばいやばい。
Crazy, crazy.
ということでですね、改めまして、Fes.「Link Your Wish」が始まりました。
And so, once again, Fes. "Link Your Wish" has begun!
そして、なんと今回初の試み、皆さん。
And, to everyone's surprise, our first ever attempt...
トロッコは見てくれましたか？
Did you see the carts?
すごかったね。
It was amazing, wasn't it?
いや、すごかったね。
Yeah, it was amazing.
いつもよりね、ちょっと我々のことが近くで見られた方々がいっぱいいるんじゃないでしょうか。
I bet there are many people who got to see us closer than usual, aren't there?
どうだった？どうだった？
How was it? How was it?
よかった？
Was it good?
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
またですね、帰宅してからでもいいですし、
Also, even after you go home,
配信見てる方はですね、ぜひともハッシュタグ、
or those watching the stream, please use the hashtag...
#ホロライブFesEXPO26Day1 で、本日、
#hololiveFesEXPO26Day1,
感想などなどいろいろとよろしくお願いします！
and please share your thoughts and impressions today!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
そして、なんと…
And, to top it off...
え、あ、あ、あれ。
Wait, oh, what was that?
早い早い、早い早い。
Too fast, too fast, too fast!
そして、なんと！配信チケット、そこの貴方、
And what's more! Online tickets, you there,
そこの、そしてそこの方々、なんと、
and you, and those people over there, what's more...
ここまで！
Up to here!
まだ見たいですよね？
You still want to watch, right?
皆様はぜひ、概要欄から配信サイトに行って、
Everyone, please visit the streaming site via the description
チケットよろしくお願いします！
and grab your tickets!
よろしくお願いします！絶対見てね！
Please do! Be sure to watch!
ま、我々もですね、まだまだユニット曲は終わってしまったんですけど、
Well, we may have finished our unit songs,
ソロ曲もありますからね！
but we still have our solo songs!
あります！絶対見てね！
We do! Be sure to watch!
この場を借りて
Using this opportunity...
もし良ければさ、みんなソロ曲の時に
if you'd like, during everyone's solo songs...
あ、ファンのみんなに何してほしいかっていうのをちょっと
Ah, we can talk about what we want the fans to do.
お！
Oh!
振りありますか？なんかペ、サイリウム？ペンライトの色何色がいいとかさ
Is there a choreo? Or what color penlight you want?
これは、オレンジ！
For me, orange!
え、オレンジ？え、嘘！
Orange?! Really?!
あ、違うのか
Oh, is that not it?
曲に合わせて、手拍子があったから
Since there's hand clapping to go with the song,
やっぱエモい感じにしてもらったりとかしてほしいな
I'd love for you to make it feel emotional.
おお、いいですね。なるほどなるほど。Watameは？
Oh, that's nice. I see, I see. What about Watame?
え、やっぱ一番でっかい声を、出してほしいなと思って
Well, I really want you to let out your loudest voice!
でっかい声！でっかい声出せるよな！
Loud voice! You guys can shout loudly, right?!
でっかい声！
Loud voice!
じゃあWatameのソロ曲の時もよろしくお願いします。そしてPolkaちゃんはどうですか？
Please do that during Watame's solo song too. And how about Polka-chan?
もちろん盛り上がってくれるよな！おお！
Of course you're going to get hyped, right?! Oh!
Polkaの時はよろしくお願いします！
Please support me during Polka's turn!
あ、そうそう。白上、ちょっとあの、ペンラに触れたんですけど
Ah, right. Shirakami, I mentioned the penlights earlier, but...
白上のソロ曲の時は是非とも皆さん、あの、白上のカラーではなく、皆さんの最推しのカラーで
during Shirakami's solo song, please don't use Shirakami's color, but use your favorite's color instead!
ええ？どうして、どうして？
Eh? Why is that?
白上推しの方は、あの、白とか、あの、でもいいですけど
Those who support Shirakami, white or whatever is fine, but...
今回のね、あのDay 1含めホロライブプロダクションに好きな推しのカラーが皆さんあると思います。
I think you all have a favorite member's color in Hololive Production, including Day 1.
白上のソロ曲の時は是非とも、皆さんの最推しのカラーで
So during Shirakami's solo song, please wave your favorite's color!
振ってくれると、多分、すっごい良い景色になるんじゃないかと思ってます。
If you do, I think it will create a really beautiful view.
白上のソロ曲もよろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to Shirakami's solo song too!
さ、じゃあ配信のみんなが
Now, let's make the stream audience...
見ている、なんかあの、うらやましい感じでみんな、イェーイ！って言ったり、配信のみんなに
jealous! Let's say "Yay!" to everyone watching on stream!
イェーイ！
Yay!
この後も盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's keep getting hyped after this!
さあ、じゃあ続いての楽曲も準備出来てるっぽいので、ね。メンバー、いきますか
Alright, it looks like the next song is ready. Members, shall we go?
じゃあ、今回皆さん、『Ridin' on Dreams』がテーマなので、これで締めたいと思います。いきますよ！
Then, since the theme this time is "Ridin' on Dreams", let's close with that. Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go...
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！